HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
NONE OF THAT, NOT WHILE
YOU'RE LIVING UNDER MY ROOF.
WHAT?
LOOK, JUST BECAUSE
I KNOW ABOUT YOU TWO
DOESN'T MEAN I LIKE
LOOKING AT IT.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE
AT AN AUDITION FOR ANOTHER HOUR?
WELL, I'M SORRY IF I'M NOT
A MIDDLE-AGED, BLACK WOMAN.
AND I'M ALSO SORRY
IF SOMETIMES I GO TO
THE WRONG AUDITION.
OKAY, LOOK, IF
I HAVE TO PRETEND
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU TWO
THEN YOU TWO ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO PRETEND
THERE'S NOTHING TO KNOW ABOUT.
OKAY. SORRY.
OKAY.
SORRY.
( soft moaning )
I CAN
HEAR THAT!
RACHEL'S AT WORK.
I CAN STILL
HEAR YOU!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY.
HELLO.
HEY. WHAT'S THAT?
MY MOM SENT ME
A FAMILY HEIRLOOM
THAT ONCE BELONGED
TO MY GRANDMOTHER.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
A YEAR AGO,
I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE A FAMILY
AND NOW I HAVE HEIRLOOMS,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
( grunting )
HEE-HEE.
OH! GOD!
AH!
OOH, SOFT.
IS THIS MINK?
YEAH.
WHY WOULD MY MOTHER
SEND ME A FUR?
DOESN'T SHE KNOW ME,
BUT AT ALL?!
PLUS, I HAVE A PERFECTLY
FINE COAT
THAT NO INNOCENT ANIMAL
SUFFERED TO MAKE.
YEAH, JUST SOME
9-YEAR-OLD FILIPINO KIDS
WHO WORKED THEIR FINGERS BLOODY
FOR 12 CENTS AN HOUR.
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
I MADE THAT UP.
HEY.
ROSS.
ROSS...
YOU CAN'T PUT
UP FLIERS IN HERE.
HOW COME?
EVERYBODY ELSE DOES.
YOU CAN'T.
WHAT IS THAT?
OH, UH...
I'M JUST GETTING RID
OF A COUPLE OF THINGS.
THIS IS ALL OF YOUR THINGS.
YES. YES, IT IS.
NO, BUT IT'S GOOD.
SEE, EMILY THINKS WE SHOULD GET
ALL NEW STUFF.
STUFF THAT'S JUST OURS,
TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, BRAND-NEW.
BASICALLY, THIS IS
A GETTING-RID-OF-ANYTHING-
RACHEL-EVER-TOUCHED SALE.
TOUCHED, USED,
SAT ON, SLEPT ON...
I'LL TAKE IT ALL.
HEY, ROSS,
YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
LOOK, IF I CAN JUST DO
WHAT EMILY WANTS
AND GET HER TO NEW YORK,
I'M SURE EVERYTHING
WILL BE FINE.
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THAT'S A LITTLE EXTREME?
AFTER WHAT I DID,
CAN YOU BLAME HER?
YOU GOT OFF EASY.
WHEN MY FRIEND, SILVIE'S HUSBAND
SAID SOMEONE ELSE'S NAME IN BED
SHE CURSED HIM
AND TURNED HIS THINGIE GREEN.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
EMILY THINKS ROSS'S FURNITURE'S
GOT "RACHEL COOTIES"?
ALL RIGHT,
CALM DOWN, JOEY.
NO. EVERYTHING'S GETTING ALL
MESSED UP, YOU KNOW?
EMILY WON'T LET ROSS SEE RACHEL.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO STOP
SEEING RACHEL.
HENCE, ROSS STOPS SEEING US.
OH, I HATE THIS.
EVERYTHING'S CHANGING.
YEAH, I KNOW,
WE'RE LOSING ROSS.
JOEY SAID "HENCE."
LOOK, I'M NOT HAPPY
ABOUT THIS, EITHER
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF
ROSS SAYS HE'S HAPPY
THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO KEEP OUR FEELINGS
ABOUT EMILY
TO OURSELVES.
ARE YOU COOL
WITH THAT?
NO.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M AN ACTOR.
I'LL ACT COOL.
OOH...
OH, GOD! STORAGE ROOMS
GIVE ME THE CREEPS.
MONICA, COME ON,
PLEASE, HURRY UP.
HONEY, PLEASE.
IF YOU WANT
THE LITTLE, ROUND WAFFLES
YOU'VE GOT TO WAIT
TILL I FIND THE LITTLE
ROUND WAFFLE IRON.
I WANT THE LITTLE,
ROUND WAFFLES.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, HERE IT IS.
RIGHT UNDERNEATH
A CAN OF BUG BOMB.
I WONDER IF THE BEST PLACE TO
PUT SOMETHING THAT COOKS FOOD
IS UNDERNEATH
THE CAN OF POISON?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL HAVE TOAST.
( both screaming )
OH, MY GOD!
AH!
FOG HIM! FOG HIM!
( screaming )
FOG HIM!
( coughing )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO
ABOUT THIS COAT.
I'LL TAKE IT.
THAT MIGHT WORK.
OOH, YEAH.
HUH? ALL RIGHT,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU'RE ON IN FIVE,
MS. MINNELLI.
NO, NO, NO. IT'S
JUST A BIT SUDDEN.
NO, IT'S GREAT, OKAY?
I AM TOTALLY ON BOARD.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, BYE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, ROSS?
NOTHING. NO, NO, UH, ACTUALLY...
GREAT NEWS.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH EMILY
AND LOOKS LIKE I'M
MOVING TO A NEW APARTMENT.
WHOO-HOO!
WHY?
WELL, HER THOUGHT IS,
AND I AGREE
FRESH, NEW FURNITURE,
WHY NOT A FRESH, NEW APARTMENT?
HER COUSIN HAS
THIS GREAT PLACE TO SUBLET.
IT'S GOT A VIEW OF THE RIVER
ON ONE SIDE
AND COLUMBIA ON THE OTHER.
THAT'S WAY UPTOWN.
THAT'S LIKE
THREE TRAINS AWAY...
WHICH IS GREAT.
I LOVE TO RIDE THAT RAIL.
SO YOU'RE REALLY OKAY WITH THIS?
YES. YES. I MEAN, IT'S
KIND OF FAR FROM WORK
BUT, UH, YOU KNOW,
I'LL GET SO MUCH DONE
ON THE COMMUTE.
I'VE BEEN GIVEN
THE GIFT OF TIME.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S SO FUNNY
'CAUSE LAST CHRISTMAS,
I GOT THE GIFT OF SPACE.
WE SHOULD GET THEM TOGETHER
AND MAKE A CONTINUUM.
NOW HE'S MOVING?
MAN, WHAT IS EMILY
DOING TO HIM?
OW!
HE'S NOT EVEN HERE!
YOU GUYS!
WE WERE JUST IN
THE STORAGE AREA
AND WE SAW THIS
REALLY CREEPY MAN.
IT WAS LIKE THIS
CRAZY-EYED, HAIRY BEAST-MAN.
HE WAS LIKE A...
LIKE A BIGFOOT
OR A YETI OR SOMETHING.
AND HE CAME AT US
WITH AN AX,
SO RACHEL
HAD TO USE A
BUG BOMB ON HIM.
YEAH, I PULLED THE TAB
AND I JUST FOGGED
HIS YETI ASS.
UH, LIKE DARK HAIR, BUSHY BEARD?
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU FOGGED DANNY.
OH, PLEASE.
WE DID NOT FOG DANNY.
WHO'S DANNY?
DANNY JUST MOVED IN DOWNSTAIRS.
YEAH, HE JUST GOT BACK
FROM THIS FOUR-MONTH TREK
IN THE ANDES.
NICE FELLA.
OH, HE'S NICE.
HE'S NICE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU ALWAYS...
STICK UP FOR THE
PEOPLE WE FOG.
YEAH.
HI.
YOU MIGHT NOT
REMEMBER US
BUT WE ARE THE GIRLS
THAT FOGGED YOU.
YEAH. WE'RE... WE'RE
REALLY SORRY
WE FOGGED YOU.
YEAH.
OKAY.
HMM.
HI. UH, JUST SO YOU KNOW
WE... WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO FOG YOU.
WE ACTUALLY THOUGHT YOU
WERE, LIKE, A YETI OR SOMETHING.
OKAY.
YES?
HI. UH, SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT WE CAN ACCEPT
YOUR ACCEPTANCE
OF OUR APOLOGY.
IT JUST DOESN'T REALLY SEEM
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
YEAH.
OKAY.
WOW. THAT GUY
IS SO RUDE.
REALLY. WHAT
IS WITH THAT GUY?
I MEAN, YOU'D FORGIVE ME
IF I FOGGED YOU.
WELL, YOU DID
A LITTLE BIT.
OH, MY GOD.
HONEY, I'M SO SORRY.
I TOTALLY FORGIVE YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH...
HEY.
SO, LISTEN, YOU KNOW
MY FRIEND CHRIS
WHO OWNS THE
CREMATORIUM?
CREMATORIUM CHRIS? SURE.
WELL, HE SAID THAT HE
WOULD CREMATE MY
FUR COAT FOR FREE
IF I, UM, YOU
KNOW, BRING IN
THE NEXT PERSON
I KNOW WHO DIES.
REALLY?
( gasping )
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, LOOK
AT THESE PELTS.
DON'T GET TOO ATTACHED.
SHE'S HAVING IT CREMATED.
WHAT?
PH-PHOEBE? HONEY?
HONEY, I KNOW YOU'RE QUIRKY
AND I GET A BIG KICK OUT OF IT.
WE ALL DO, ACTUALLY.
BUT IF YOU DESTROY
A COAT LIKE THIS--
I MEAN, THAT IS LIKE
A CRIME AGAINST NATURE.
NO, NOT NATURE. FASHION.
THIS IS FASHION?
OKAY, SO TO YOU,
DEATH IS FASHION.
THAT'S REALLY FUNNY.
YEAH. HERE'S... HERE'S PHOEBE
UH, SPORTING, YOU KNOW,
A CUTTING-EDGE, HAIRY CARCASS
FROM, YOU KNOW, THE STEEL TRAPS
OF WINTRY RUSSIA.
I MEAN, YOU REALLY THINK
THIS LOOKS GOOD?
'CAUSE I DO.
YEAH. UH-HUH.
I KNOW. I MISS YOU, TOO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
I LOVE YOU. BYE.
OKAY, WHAT IS IN HERE, ROCKS?
OH, NO. THIS IS MY COLLECTION
OF, UH, FOSSIL SAMPLES.
SO ROCKS.
I'M REALLY GOING
TO MISS THIS APARTMENT.
YOU KNOW, BEN... BEN
TOOK HIS FIRST STEPS
RIGHT OVER THERE.
HMM.
HEY, REMEMBER WHEN I
RAN INTO THIS THING
AND IT KIND
OF KNOCKED ME OUT
A LITTLE, HUH?
I LOVE THIS PLACE.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO MOVE.
UH, ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU'RE
NOT ENTIRELY HAPPY
ABOUT THIS?
WELL, I MEAN,
IF, UH...
IF EMILY GAVE
ME A CHOICE...
YOU DO HAVE A CHOICE.
ROSS, WHY ARE YOU
LISTENING TO HER?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT?
WELL, IT'S NOT RIGHT,
WHAT EMILY WANTS YOU TO DO.
SHE IS TOTALLY... OW!
STOP PINCHING ME.
LOOK, NOW, YOU GUYS SAID
I ONLY HAVE TO
KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT
AS LONG AS ROSS
WAS HAPPY, RIGHT?
WELL, HE
JUST TOLD ME
THAT HE'S NOT
ENTIRELY HAPPY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE ALL HATE EMILY.
NO.
NO. ROSS,
WE DO NOT HATE EMILY.
WE JUST...
WE JUST THINK
THAT YOU'RE HAVING TO SACRIFICE
A WHOLE LOT TO MAKE HER HAPPY.
YEAH.
WE JUST THINK
THAT MAYBE SHE'S BEING
A LITTLE... UNREASONABLE.
YES. YES.
UNREASONABLE.
UNREASONABLE?
HOW ABOUT WE HAVE
THIS CONVERSATION
WHEN ONE OF YOU GUYS
GETS MARRIED?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT TAKES
TO MAKE A MARRIAGE WORK.
IT'S ABOUT COMPROMISE.
DO YOU ALWAYS LIKE IT? NO.
DO YOU DO IT? YES.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT ALL LAUGHING,
HAPPY, CANDY-IN-THE-SKY
DRINKING-COFFEE-AT-CENTRAL-PERK
ALL THE TIME.
IT'S REAL
LIFE, OKAY?
IT'S WHAT GROWNUPS DO.
I THINK HE'S RIGHT.
YOU GUYS HANG OUT
AT THE COFFEEHOUSE WAY TOO MUCH.
GOD, I FEEL SO GUILTY
ABOUT ROSS.
I KNOW.
I KIND OF FEEL
LIKE IT'S MY FAULT.
KIND OF?
IF YOU HAD JUST KEPT THIS
TO YOURSELF, NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
WELL, I'M KEEPING SO MANY THINGS
TO MYSELF THESE DAYS
SOMETHING WAS BOUND TO SLIP OUT.
WELL, I THINK
IT'S VERY BRAVE
WHAT YOU SAID.
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT. I CAN'T
SIT HERE ANYMORE.
I HAVE TO WALK PLACES.
PHEEBS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THE COAT?
HOW ABOUT THE WHOLE
ANIMAL RIGHTS THING?
WELL, I'VE BEEN READING UP,
AND FOR YOUR INFORMATION
MINKS ARE NOT VERY NICE.
OKAY, I ADMIT IT,
I LOVE THIS COAT, OKAY.
IT'S THE BEST THING
I'VE EVER HAD WRAPPED AROUND ME
INCLUDING PHIL HUNTLEY.
REMEMBER PHIL HUNTLEY?
HE WAS FINE.
HI.
SO, YOU LIKE
THE SHORT HAIR BETTER?
WHAT?
YETI... DANNY?!
HAD TO CUT MY HAIR TO GET RID
OF THE, UH... FOGGER SMELL.
OH.
LISTEN, OH, I'M SO SORRY.
I WOULD-I WOULD
HAVE NEVER FOGGED YOU
YOU KNOW, IF YOU HADN'T
LOOKED SO, YOU KNOW, UH...
ABSOLUTELY.
SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST
INTO APPEARANCES.
WHAT?
THAT'S COOL.
WHOA! WHOA! NO!
NO, THAT IS NOT COOL.
YOU-YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW ME.
COME ON. YOU'VE GOT
THE SHOPPING BAGS
AND THE SAKS CATALOGUE.
SO, UH, FROM THAT,
YOU THINK
YOU'VE GOT ME
ALL FIGURED OUT?!
WELL, YOU DON'T.
YOU KNOW, I COULD HAVE TOYS FOR
UNDERPRIVILEGED KIDS IN HERE.
DO YOU?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF KIDS
LIKE TO PLAY WITH CAPRI PANTS.
OKAY.
AND STOP SAYING THAT.
I HATE THAT.
OKAY.
FINE.
I JUDGED YOU.
I MADE A SNAP JUDGMENT,
BUT YOU DID IT, TOO
AND YOU'RE WORSE, BECAUSE
YOU ARE STICKING TO YOUR
STUPID SNAP JUDGMENT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN
OPEN UP YOUR MIND
FOR A SECOND
TO SEE THAT YOU
MIGHT BE WRONG.
WHAT DOES THAT
SAY ABOUT YOU?
THAT PIZZA PLACE
ACROSS THE STREET ANY GOOD?
WHAT?
I'M HUNGRY.
WANT TO GET SOME PIZZA?
YOU CAN KEEP YELLING
IF THERE'S MORE.
OKAY.
STOP SAYING THAT.
I HATE THAT.
UH, ROSS...
ARE YOU STILL
MAD AT US?
YUP.
OH, GOOD, 'CAUSE WE HAVE
AN "I'M SORRY" SONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M REALLY NOT IN THE MOOD.
LOOK, ROSS,
I FEEL REALLY BAD.
I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH ALL THIS STUFF
AND... I JUST ACTED
LIKE A JERK.
YEAH, WE ARE SO SORRY.
YOU'RE KIND OF
STEPPING ON THE SONG.
LOOK... WE WERE WAY
OUT OF LINE, ALL RIGHT?
WE TOTALLY SUPPORT YOU.
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE,
WHATEVER YOU DO.
OKAY, NOW YOU'RE JUST TAKING
LINES RIGHT OUT OF THE SONG.
LOOK, THIS IS HARD ENOUGH, OKAY.
I REALLY NEED YOU GUYS
RIGHT NOW.
YES. EXACTLY.
AND THAT'S WHY...
( strums two notes )
WHY DON'T YOU
COME OVER TONIGHT
AND I'LL MAKE YOU
YOUR FAVORITE DINNER?
COME ON.
OKAY.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
PHEEBS, ARE YOU
WEARING FUR?
OKAY, LET'S GET SOME
PERSPECTIVE, PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M WEARING
A SEEING-EYE DOG COAT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, ROSS
I, UH... I THINK
I KIND OF UNDERSTAND
WHY I KIND OF LOST IT TODAY.
YOU DO, HUH?
YEAH, YOU SEE,
I'M AN ACTOR, RIGHT?
SO I GOT TO KEEP MY EMOTIONS
RIGHT AT THE SURFACE, YOU KNOW?
I GOT A LOT OF BALLS IN THE AIR,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S TOUGH. GUYS LIKE ME,
YOU KNOW, YOU WANDER AROUND--
YOU'RE ALONE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M NOT SURE.
HI.
HEY, LOOK AT YOU.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
OH, I WENT TO HAVE
PIZZA WITH DANNY.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
THAT YETI IS ONE SMOOTH TALKER.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT TOO FULL,
'CAUSE DINNER'S ALMOST READY.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, I THINK
I'M PROBABLY JUST GOING
TO HANG OUT IN ROOM.
OH, NO.
WHY?
COME ON,
YOU GUYS.
IF EMILY KNEW I WAS HERE
HAVING DINNER WITH YOU
SHE WOULD FLIP OUT
AND YOU KNOW IT.
IT'S OKAY.
I REALLY... I DON'T MIND.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? JUST STAY.
PLEASE. IT WOULD REALLY MEAN
A LOT FOR ME IF YOU STAY.
ROSS, I JUST...
RACHEL, PLEASE.
JUST HAVE DINNER WITH US.
OKAY, OKAY, JOEY, IT'S OKAY.
SETTLE DOWN.
ALL RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
YOU SEE, RACH, I'M AN ACTOR.
HEY!
HEY, LOOK,
THE UGLY NAKED GUY'S BACK.
OH, MY GOD!
WE HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
IN SO LONG.
OH, GOD, I REALLY MISSED
THAT FAT BASTARD.
WOW. THIS IS
SO WEIRD.
I JUST REALIZED THIS
MAY BE THE LAST TIME
WE'RE ALL HANGING
OUT TOGETHER.
IT'S ALMOST
AS IF HE KNEW.
( phone ringing )
I'LL GET IT.
HELLO.
HI, EMILY.
YEAH, YOU TRACKED HIM DOWN.
HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
HEY.
YEAH, YEAH,
WE'RE, UH...
WE'RE JUST
HAVING DINNER.
UH, YEAH, SURE. HOLD ON.
SHE WANTS TO SAY HI.
HOLD ON.
All:
HI, EMILY.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
SO, WHO AM I SAYING HELLO TO?
WELL, UH...
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
WHO'S HERE
BUT I CAN TELL YOU
FOR DAMN SURE
WHO'S NOT HERE,
AND THAT'S RACHEL.
Well, I should hope not.
Ross knows better
than that by now.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
RACHEL IS HERE.
She's there?
OH, YEAH, THERE SHE IS.
YEAH, YEAH, SHE'S HERE.
ROSS, TAKE ME OFF SPEAKER PHONE.
HI.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?
I THOUGHT I'D MADE MY FEELINGS
ABOUT RACHEL PERFECTLY CLEAR.
LOOK, EMILY, I'M JUST HAVING
DINNER WITH MY FRIENDS, OKAY?
YOU OBVIOUSLY CAN'T
KEEP AWAY FROM HER.
Emily, that's ridiculous.
LOOK, I'M MOVING FOR YOU.
I'M CUTTING FRIENDS
OUT OF MY LIFE FOR YOU.
PLEASE, JUST GET ON THE PLANE
AND COME TO NEW YORK, OKAY?
YOU'LL SEE.
You're the only person
I want to be with.
I'LL FEEL BETTER WHEN I'M THERE
AND I CAN KNOW WHERE YOU ARE
ALL THE TIME.
WELL, YOU...
YOU CAN'T KNOW WHERE I AM
ALL THE TIME.
LOOK, THIS MARRIAGE IS
NEVER GOING TO WORK
IF YOU DON'T TRUST ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO... CAN YOU TRUST ME?
NO.
I THINK IT'S
GOING OKAY.
YEAH, LOOKS LIKE
HE'S SMILING.
HOW CAN YOU TELL?
YOU CAN ONLY SEE
THE BACK OF HIS HEAD.
YOU CAN TOTALLY TELL.
HERE, LOOK, WATCH ME.
SMILE. FROWN.
SMILE.
FROWN... SMILE...
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S IT.
Phoebe:
WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
MY MARRIAGE IS OVER.
Monica:
SWEETIE...
OH, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE SHIVERING.
HERE.
ROSS, HONEY, IS THERE
ANYTHING WE CAN DO?
YEAH.
YOU CAN HELP ME GET
MY FURNITURE BACK FROM GUNTHER.
( whistling tune )
OKAY, STOP TORMENTING ME!
THIS IS MINK, OKAY?
THEY'RE MEAN
AND THEY HATE SQUIRRELS.
AND, YOU KNOW, OKAY
MOST OF THESE PROBABLY
WANTED TO BE COATS.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
NO, I GET IT.
HERE, YOU TAKE IT.
ARE YOU HAPPY NOW?
I'M COLD!